{
    "subject": "resource/Kano_(Mortal_Kombat)",
    "predicate": "property/liveactor",
    "object": "resource/Trevor_Goddard",
    "human_readable": "Kano was played by Trevor Goddard.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9689803123474121,
            "question": "In what movie or series did Trevor Goddard portray Kano?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8617488741874695,
            "question": "What role did Trevor Goddard play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8109511733055115,
            "question": "Who played the character Kano?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6704257130622864,
            "question": "Is Trevor Goddard known for playing action roles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5530080199241638,
            "question": "Are there other actors who have played Kano?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4722024202346802,
            "question": "What are some of Trevor Goddard's other notable roles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4378247857093811,
            "question": "What is the character Kano known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22567573189735413,
            "question": "Is Kano a protagonist or antagonist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20743559300899506,
            "question": "When was Kano first introduced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14552561938762665,
            "question": "What genre is Kano typically associated with?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kano was played by Trevor Goddard.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1472_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was Kano first introduced?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1472_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Kano a protagonist or antagonist?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1472_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the character Kano known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1472_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1472_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1472_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1472_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1472_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1472_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1472_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1472_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1472_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1472_94.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1472_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Trevor Goddard played the role of Kano in the first Mortal Kombat film, which directly supports the triple \"Kano was played by Trevor Goddard.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}